<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260528134500 -0400" stop="20260528141500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>A burglary investigation at Kevin's university reveals Holt's hidden insecurity. Amy and Terry's efforts to raise morale turn deliciously cutthroat.</desc><sub-title>The Bimbo</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260528134048 -0400" stop="20260528140446 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>Jack asks Liz to deal with a group of German TV execs so he can spend more time with C.C. but Liz has fallen in love with a piece of real estate. Tracy buys a cappuccino machine and gets Kenneth addicted to caffeine.</desc><sub-title>Episode 210</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260528123331 -0400" stop="20260528142435 -0400"><title>Sing</title><desc>In a city of humanoid animals, a hustling theater impresario's attempt to save his theater with a singing competition becomes grander than he anticipates even as its finalists find that their lives will never be the same.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260528181500 +0100" stop="20260528190000 +0100"><title>House</title><desc>While a severely burned teenager is admitted and his blood tests come back with strange results, House makes himself the guinea pig in his own unofficial tests of a new drug designed to treat migraines to prove a former medical school colleague is wrong about the drug.</desc><sub-title>Distractions</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260528134504 -0400" stop="20260528143846 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Gordon pays a visit to Oscars in Nantwich. On the surface this place seems idyllic - an Irish family-run restaurant in the heart of beautiful countryside. Owner Maura runs the front of house and her son Lenin is head chef, but it's not happy families. With her life savings on the line Maura is in big trouble. She constantly bickers with her son whilst the customers are forced to wait hours for their fluorescent crab stick paellas, and stodgy carbonaras from Oscar's 'bit of everything' menu. The place is losing &#163;2,000 per week, but that isn't the worst of their problems - Lenin has got a serious drink problem and during service collapses and has to be rushed off to hospital. It's Gordon's toughest challenge yet. Can he bring the Irish heart back to Oscars, stop mother and son fighting, and get Lenin to face up to his problems?</desc><sub-title>Oscar's Restaurant</sub-title></programme></tv>