<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524090000 -0400" stop="20260524093000 -0400"><title>3rd Rock from the Sun</title><desc>Once again, Mary's father (George) has left his wife and has come to stay with Mary. When the Solomons are over for a visit, George and Sally get along well. Very well indeed... Meanwhile, Harry and Tommy find the vacant university radio studio and start broadcasts. Harry doesn't exactly make a lot of friends with his idea of talk radio.</desc><sub-title>My Daddy's Little Girl</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524091508 -0400" stop="20260524093927 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Jake and Terry try to solve an apparently unsolvable case, Amy lies to Holt in order to dodge work and escape for a romantic weekend away, while Gina and Rosa introduce Charles to "Babylon", their secret bathroom.</desc><sub-title>Unsolvable</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524090312 -0400" stop="20260524110258 -0400"><title>Cars</title><desc>While traveling to California for the dispute of the final race of the Piston Cup against The King and Chick Hicks, the famous Lightning McQueen accidentally damages the road of the small town Radiator Springs and is sentenced to repair it. Lightning McQueen has to work hard and finds friendship and love in the simple locals, changing its values during his stay in the small town and becoming a true winner.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524140000 +0100" stop="20260524150000 +0100"><title>Tipping Point</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 42</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524085952 -0400" stop="20260524095233 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Think the MythBusters always get it right the first time? In this episode, Jamie and Adam...with a little help from some viewers, revisit some of the most popular and controversial myths to find out if they can put their own experiements to the test!</desc><sub-title>Myths Revisited</sub-title></programme></tv>