<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517093000 -0400" stop="20260517100000 -0400"><title>Frasier</title><desc>Frasier's budding romance is complicated by a stripper; Maris tries to sabotage Niles' new relationship.</desc><sub-title>To Thine Old Self Be True</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517094421 -0400" stop="20260517100819 -0400"><title>Archer (2009)</title><desc>Malory hosts a dinner party for the UN intelligence chairman, Torvald Utne, in an effort to get a new weapons contract for ISIS. Unfortunately, a group of rival assassins have targeted Mr. Utne for elimination.</desc><sub-title>Killing Utne</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517093315 -0400" stop="20260517111930 -0400"><title>Kiki's Delivery Service</title><desc>Along with her black cat Jiji, Kiki settles in a seaside town and starts a high-flying delivery service. Here begins her magical encounter with independence and responsibility, making lifelong friends and finding her place in the world.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517140000 +0100" stop="20260517150000 +0100"><title>Tipping Point</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 35</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517094715 -0400" stop="20260517101355 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>At the Abbey House in Penrith, Cumbria, Ian and Samantha Sugden pride themselves on their simple but scrupulously clean rooms.

The rivals then travel to Compton House in Newark, Nottinghamshire, where sisters Lisa Holloway and Becky Waltman offer antique filled rooms and five star breakfasts.

The third visit is to the White Horse Inn in Ripon, Yorkshire managed by Dave and Jo Bate. Their basic rooms, and pub breakfasts don't impress though.

Last is the Old Farmhouse, Chester, run by retired teachers Ed and Jane Mitchell.</desc><sub-title>From Abbey House to the Old Farmhouse</sub-title></programme></tv>