<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516083000 -0400" stop="20260516091500 -0400"><title>3rd Rock from the Sun</title><desc>Tommy and Harry find a wallet and return it to the owner who doesn't give them a reward for it. After Mrs. Dubcek tells them a trifle is the least he could do, they try to get their reward after all. Meanwhile, Dick feels ready to start dating again and after some advice from Sally he and Officer Don go on a double date. Sally also has a date and wonders how much a man will bear before having had enough of her.</desc><sub-title>The Great Dickdater</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516000137 -0400" stop="20260517000158 -0400"><title>OFF-AIR</title><desc /><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516085534 -0400" stop="20260516103822 -0400"><title>KPop Demon Hunters</title><desc>A world-renowned K-Pop girl group balances their lives in the spotlight with their secret identities as bad-ass demon hunters, set against a colorful backdrop of fashion, food, style, and the most popular music movement of the current generation.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260516134500 +0100" stop="20260516141500 +0100"><title>Fate/Apocrypha</title><desc>Despite harboring doubts about her unusual summoning, Ruler heads to the battleground in Trifas, Romania, to preside over the Great Holy Grail War.</desc><sub-title>The Saint Departs</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516082605 -0400" stop="20260516091902 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Jamie and Adam try to scientifically explain the recently publicized and highly entertaining chemical reaction caused as a result of placing a Mentos candy into a 2-liter bottle of Diet Coke. The rest of the Mythbusters team explores the possibility of a standard postage stamp causing enough imbalance in the rotating assemblies of a helicopter to cause it to crash.</desc><sub-title>Mentos and Soda</sub-title></programme></tv>