<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530174500 -0400" stop="20260530183000 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>Monk goes up against a Bobby Fisher-type chess genius who always appears to be two steps ahead of Monk.</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk and the Genius</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530173940 -0400" stop="20260530180715 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>In the second season finale, Jack moves on to a new job involving politics in Washington, but the position is not quite what he anticipated. Meanwhile, Liz suffers a pregnancy scare, Kenneth confronts rival page Donny when applying for a summer job, and Tracy works on his latest invention.</desc><sub-title>Cooter</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530172551 -0400" stop="20260530191601 -0400"><title>Whiplash</title><desc>A promising young drummer enrolls at a cut-throat music conservatory where his dreams of greatness are mentored by an instructor who will stop at nothing to realize a student's potential.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530223000 +0100" stop="20260530230000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>Shinji says things like how he has no intention of fighting and he was just dragged into this war. He asks to make an alliance with Shirou to go after Rin but Shirou refuses. Shinji says because he doesn't know magic other Masters can't detect him so that means Shinji isn't the other Master Rin was detecting, meaning there is a fourth one at the school. Before Shirou leaves Shinji tells Shirou about how one of the Masters has set up base at a temple.Shirou gets home and is yelled at by Saber and Rin, Rin having come over after Shirou didn't come home. Shirou tells them about Shinji and the Master at the temple.Shirou and Rin both agree, against Sabers judgment, that they should not attack the temple yet as they don't know what Servant and it may be a trap.Saber brings up again with Shirou the temple but Shirou insists that they won't be going.</desc><sub-title>Discordant Melody</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530170036 -0400" stop="20260530175249 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Jamie and Adam try to scientifically explain the recently publicized and highly entertaining chemical reaction caused as a result of placing a Mentos candy into a 2-liter bottle of Diet Coke. The rest of the Mythbusters team explores the possibility of a standard postage stamp causing enough imbalance in the rotating assemblies of a helicopter to cause it to crash.</desc><sub-title>Mentos and Soda</sub-title></programme></tv>