<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530193000 -0400" stop="20260530200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Susmita offers to help Tina with a photography class assignment, but Tina can't stop thinking about all the fun Tammy, Jocelyn, Zeke and Jimmy Jr. are having ditching class. Meanwhile, a woman who used to live in the Belchers' apartment comes for a visit.</desc><sub-title>FOMO You Didn't</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530185228 -0400" stop="20260530205839 -0400"><title>Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues</title><desc>With the 1970s behind him, Ron Burgundy, San Diego's former top-rated newsreader, returns to take New York City's first twenty-four-hour news channel by storm.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530191601 -0400" stop="20260530210133 -0400"><title>Ponyo</title><desc>When Sosuke, a young boy who lives on a clifftop overlooking the sea, rescues a stranded goldfish named Ponyo, he discovers more than he bargained for. Ponyo is a curious, energetic young creature who yearns to be human, but even as she causes chaos around the house, her father, a powerful sorcerer, schemes to return Ponyo to the sea.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531003000 +0100" stop="20260531010000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>From the moon, Megatron manages to interfere with the radio transmissions on Earth. Blaster and Cosmos go to put an end to his plot as the other Autobots work to help those affected by the loss of radio transmissions.</desc><sub-title>Blaster Blues</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530193822 -0400" stop="20260530200629 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Brock Bergius hopes his cheeky sense of humour and perfectionist nature will help make the guests' third visit of the competition, to York House in Tetbury, Gloucestershire, the winning one.

During an afternoon of sausage making, Brock is in his element making saucy jokes. But his reluctance to go 'off-menu' at breakfast leaves some guests a bit disappointed.</desc><sub-title>York House</sub-title></programme></tv>