<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260525014500 -0400" stop="20260525023000 -0400"><title>Stargate SG-1</title><desc>In escaping a large contingent of Jaffa, SG-1 is forced to leave behind Jack and Lt. Tyler, a new member of the team. Back on Earth no one can recall Lt. Tyler, so Sam, Teal'c, and Daniel must find a way to save Jack while they are quarantined. Meanwhile Jack and Lt. Tyler struggle to escape the enemy Jaffa.</desc><sub-title>The Fifth Man</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260525014600 -0400" stop="20260525021045 -0400"><title>The Goldbergs (2013)</title><desc>When Beverly learns that Barry lied about joining the wrestling team, she takes matters into her own hands; Erica flakes on a promise to take Adam to the premiere of "Return of the Jedi.</desc><sub-title>A Wrestler Named Goldberg</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260525015441 -0400" stop="20260525033215 -0400"><title>Wayne's World</title><desc>Two slacker friends try to promote their public-access cable show.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260525015318 -0400" stop="20260525022103 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Showmen Mike and Danny host their rival B&amp;B owners on day four at their four-star rated guest house - Homecliffe Hotel - in Blackpool.

After everyone is settled in, Mike and Danny want to show their guests that Blackpool rocks. First up is a tram ride along the sea front and then onto the newly-opened Madame Tussauds.

After a red carpet afternoon it's on to dinner at Mike's favourite restaurant - his own. Over dinner the cracks between the Homecliffe boys and Tim and Amelia really begin to show.

In the morning there are reports from some guests of dodgy mattresses and a restless night's sleep. And breakfast isn't much more of a success, with Mike forced to send one of his staff to find some Earl Grey tea from another B&amp;B for Amelia and Eva.</desc><sub-title>Homecliffe Hotel, Blackpool</sub-title></programme></tv>