<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531070000 -0400" stop="20260531073000 -0400"><title>Cheers</title><desc>Rebecca parties hearty to hide her second thoughts after Robin finally pops the question and Frasier develops a passion for the new sing-along machine.</desc><sub-title>The Days of Wine and Neuroses (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531053825 -0400" stop="20260531073257 -0400"><title>22 Jump Street</title><desc>After making their way through high school (twice), big changes are in store for officers Schmidt and Jenko when they go deep undercover at a local college.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531054228 -0400" stop="20260531074045 -0400"><title>28 Years Later</title><desc>A group of survivors of the rage virus live on a small island. When one of the group leaves the island on a mission into the mainland, he discovers secrets, wonders, and horrors that have mutated not only the infected but other survivors.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531120000 +0100" stop="20260531130000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Gordon travels to the seaside in aid of hotel and restaurant the Sandgate. This is happily married couple Lois and Peters' first venture into the catering industry. They used to enjoy eating in restaurants, so thought it might be fun to own one. A year and a half later their dream has turned into a nightmare - they're losing &#163;4,000 a month. In the kitchen, their head chef Stuart is on the brink of a nervous breakdown. He's forced to cook for four restaurants, including fine dining upstairs and Japanese fare in the basement. But it's when he loses his coveted AA award that he really hits rock bottom. Eccentric, overstaffed and on the point of collapse, can Gordon bring this real life Fawlty Towers back from the edge?</desc><sub-title>Sandgate Hotel</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531070839 -0400" stop="20260531073445 -0400"><title>Mind Field</title><desc>How much of the sensations we feel is determined by our physical bodies? Maybe our minds play a bigger role than we know. I&#8217;ll see if people can be tricked into feeling intense physical pain, even though it&#8217;s all in their heads. I&#8217;ll also look at a machine that makes it possible for you to tickle yourself, and I&#8217;ll show you a weird physical illusion you can do at home.</desc><sub-title>Touch</sub-title></programme></tv>