<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260528161500 -0400" stop="20260528170000 -0400"><title>Bones</title><desc>Brennan and Booth investigate human remains found at a neighborhood block party. Suburban politics and secret scandals give each neighbor in the cul-de-sac a motive, leaving Brennan, Booth and Sweets to sift through the drama to find their suspect. Meanwhile, Jeffersonian intern Arastoo comes clean about his background, and Booth's son attempts to find Booth a girlfriend.</desc><sub-title>The Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260528152020 -0400" stop="20260528171513 -0400"><title>Scott Pilgrim vs. the World</title><desc>As bass guitarist for a garage-rock band, Scott Pilgrim has never had trouble getting a girlfriend; usually, the problem is getting rid of them. But when Ramona Flowers skates into his heart, he finds she has the most troublesome baggage of all: an army of ex-boyfriends who will stop at nothing to eliminate him from her list of suitors.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260528142435 -0400" stop="20260528163818 -0400"><title>Iron Man 3</title><desc>When Tony Stark's world is torn apart by a formidable terrorist called the Mandarin, he starts an odyssey of rebuilding and retribution.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260528210500 +0100" stop="20260528220000 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>After being brought back to life in The Parting of the Ways, Captain Jack Harkness was just left on the Gamestation by the Doctor and Rose. In this episode, Captain Jack Harkness storms back into the Doctor's life, and the TARDIS is thrown to the end of the universe itself.</desc><sub-title>Utopia (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260528155825 -0400" stop="20260528162617 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Day three of the competition takes place in York, where part time panto dame Graham Smith runs The Georgian House and Mews and takes his guests back in time with a Nordic test of strength in the afternoon.

At supper, Graham is lyrical and Hazel has romance on her mind, and at breakfast the guests fend for themselves until Graham makes a show stopping appearance.</desc><sub-title>The Georgian House and Mews</sub-title></programme></tv>