<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520080000 -0400" stop="20260520083000 -0400"><title>The King of Queens</title><desc>Doug sabotages Carrie's attempts to start hanging out with her co-workers by scaring them off with several crude techniques. Meanwhile, Spence and Danny realize that women like men who take care of the elderly and start using Arthur as bait.</desc><sub-title>Tank Heaven</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520081723 -0400" stop="20260520084101 -0400"><title>Archer (2009)</title><desc>In yet another attempt to secure funding for ISIS, Malory drags her agents to the luxury winter resort town of Gstaad to protect a Swiss billionaire's daughter from a kidnapping threat. But Archer soon finds out the real threat is his protectee: an underage nymphomaniac who will stop at nothing to bed the world&#8217;s greatest spy.</desc><sub-title>Swiss Miss</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260520075758 -0400" stop="20260520095141 -0400"><title>Ratatouille</title><desc>A rat who can cook makes an unusual alliance with a young kitchen worker at a famous Paris restaurant.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520130000 +0100" stop="20260520133000 +0100"><title>Lucky Star</title><desc>It's Konata's birthday, and her family sets up a surprise party for her when she gets home from work.  All goes according to plan until Konata calls and says that her coworkers are throwing her a party and that she'll be coming home late.

The girls discuss what their goals in life are.

Kagami has a bad day when she gets bothered by little annoyances and ends up going to a store to buy a drink but forgets her wallet.

Things get worse for Kagami when her older sister Matsuri scolds her for neglecting to buy groceries for dinner.

On Lucky Channel, Akira and Shiraishi have a special guest: Meito Anizawa, the manager of the anime store that desperately wants Konata to buy something from his shop.  He talks about the three factors that determine an anime's success.</desc><sub-title>At the Base of the Sun</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520073743 -0400" stop="20260520082436 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Actors Kristen Bell and Dax Shepard face off in a series of Battle of the Sexes games designed to illustrate the differences between female and male brains.</desc><sub-title>Male Brain vs. Female Brain</sub-title></programme></tv>