<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517161500 -0400" stop="20260517170000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>A victim of a mugging presents with neurological symptoms and begins to mirror the behaviors of his doctors. Foreman joins the new fellows in seeking a diagnosis; Cameron and Chase takes bets on whom House will fire next.</desc><sub-title>Mirror Mirror</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517151152 -0400" stop="20260517164910 -0400"><title>Wayne's World 2</title><desc>Wayne is back, this time trying to organize a rock festival with help from friend Garth and the spirit of Jim Morrison (Doors). Meanwhile, his girlfriend's manager is busy trying to woo her away from Wayne and move her to LA. Life gets interesting when Wayne must rush from the concert to try and stop the wedding. Aerosmith are featured at the concert.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517153428 -0400" stop="20260517175744 -0400"><title>Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith</title><desc>As the Clone Wars nears its end, Obi-Wan Kenobi pursues a new threat, while Anakin Skywalker is lured by Chancellor Palpatine into a sinister plot for galactic domination.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517211500 +0100" stop="20260517221500 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>One year has passed since the events of "The Sound of Drums." The Earth has been conquered and its population enslaved, the Doctor is the Master's prisoner, and the warships of a new Time Lord Empire rise from the ashes. The fate of the world is in Martha Jones' hands.</desc><sub-title>Last of the Time Lords (3)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517162443 -0400" stop="20260517164921 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Scuba Diving Lights, Interchangeable Sandals, Race Car Simulators, and Fibreglass Doors and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Scuba Lights, Interchangeable Sandals, Race Car Simulators, Fibreglass Doors</sub-title></programme></tv>