<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517193000 -0400" stop="20260517200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Tina competes against Gene and Louise to write a new school song for Wagstaff but finds herself creatively stalled. Meanwhile, Bob and Linda battle blinding glare from Jimmy Pesto's new shiny steel awning across the street.</desc><sub-title>Wag the Song</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517193811 -0400" stop="20260517200257 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie tries to infiltrate the boys' club of politics by crashing an after-work gathering at the town hall. Trying to fit in, she opens a gift basket breaking the local government ethics, and then is called before an ethics committee.</desc><sub-title>Boys' Club</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517191641 -0400" stop="20260517213911 -0400"><title>Everything Everywhere All at Once</title><desc>Having moved from China, a middle-aged woman finds herself entangled in a wild journey. She alone holds the key to preserving reality, as she traverses alternate universes and encounters the various lives she might have lived.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260518001500 +0100" stop="20260518004500 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>Some Autobots take part in a charity race in Europe, but it's all a Decepticon ploy to obtain metal from Augie Canay's car in order to house the Pearl of Bahoudin. With their teammates damaged by the Stunticons, it will be up to Bumblebee, Bluestreak and Tracks to stop the Decepticon plot.</desc><sub-title>Trans-Europe Express</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517192829 -0400" stop="20260517195538 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The first visit of this new competition is to Blackthorn Farm on Anglesey, where best friends Richard Tuke and Susan Hatch hope to impress, but there are mixed reactions at feedback time.</desc><sub-title>Blackthorn Farm</sub-title></programme></tv>