<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524170000 -0400" stop="20260524174500 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>House copes with a patient whose symptoms conceal a greater problem, but spends much of his time dodging Cuddy's orders to give performance reviews, and fighting with Amber over who gets to spend more time with Wilson.</desc><sub-title>No More Mr. Nice Guy</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524172309 -0400" stop="20260524174647 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>The Lopez family finds out that Benny's estranged brother, Uncle Joe is dying. George and Angie convince Benny to reconcile with Uncle Joe-but Benny's more interested in getting Joe's Super Bowl tickets. Meanwhile, since Benny never taught George how to cope with death when he was younger, he has difficulty attending the funeral.</desc><sub-title>Super Bowl</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524164806 -0400" stop="20260524181318 -0400"><title>Big City Greens the Movie: Spacecation</title><desc>When thrill-seeker Cricket tricks his family into taking a "road trip" in space, chaos in the cosmos quickly ensues. Despite growing frustrations between Cricket and his dad, Bill, the two must learn to appreciate each other's unique perspectives in order to prevent Big City from being destroyed by an interstellar disaster.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524223000 +0100" stop="20260524230000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>Saber yelled at Shirou for not summoning her when he was in danger. Saber starts to go to school with Shirou. When Rin appears and says she will walk with Shirou to school, Saber allowing this after Rin talked to her. She explained that this way enemies may think it's a trap to not see Saber with him so they are less likely to attack.Rin explains that there should be spell marks around the school and if they destroy those it will delay the activation of the force field but not destroy it, and most likely force the master out of hiding. After school Shirou and Rin work to find spell marks and destroy them. They end up destroying a good amount of them and call it a night.On the way home, before Shirou gets anywhere but after Rin leaves he feels something really strong. He goes to investigate it and feels its coming from the archery club.</desc><sub-title>Despicable Act</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524171705 -0400" stop="20260524174533 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The guests head to Scotland to stay with final host Caroline at The Dean B&amp;B, a picturesque house with breath-taking views across the Firth of Forth.

Determined to give her guests a bonnie day out, Caroline's opening gambit is a jig accompanied by a bagpiper, followed by a re-enactment of the Battle of Prestonpans in gale-force winds.

The group don their glad rags for a posh dinner at one of Scotland's finest restaurants, although some feel their portions aren't nearly big enough.

The guests' Highland dining experiences don't improve when it comes to breakfast at The Dean, which features uncooked eggs and mouldy jam.

Caroline is reduced to tears reading her guests' comments on the feedback forms. Who will be feeling the emotion when it comes to payment time?</desc><sub-title>The Dean. Firth of Forth</sub-title></programme></tv>