<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524123000 -0400" stop="20260524131500 -0400"><title>Kitchen Nightmares (US)</title><desc>Ramsay helps the owners of Old Neighborhood in Arvada, Colo., transform their restaurant.</desc><sub-title>Old Neighborhood</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524123526 -0400" stop="20260524125804 -0400"><title>Everybody Hates Chris</title><desc>Rochelle and Julius don't have enough money to get Chris his new Walkman that he wants for Christmas. Drew tells Toyna the truth about Santa Claus, which makes Tonya question about other things her mom and dad told her.</desc><sub-title>Everybody Hates Christmas</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524123253 -0400" stop="20260524141028 -0400"><title>The Secret World of Arrietty</title><desc>The Clock family consists of three four-inch-tall people who live incognito among humans, borrowing only what they need to survive. Their quiet life changes when their teenage daughter, Arrietty, is discovered.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524173000 +0100" stop="20260524180000 +0100"><title>Would I Lie to You?</title><desc>Host Angus Deayton joins regular team captains David Mitchell and Lee Mack for the show all about truths and lies, with guest panellists Graeme Garden, Lauren Laverne, Phil Daniels and Michael McIntyre</desc><sub-title>Graeme Garden, Lauren Laverne, Phil Daniels, Michael McIntyre</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524123143 -0400" stop="20260524132445 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Mexican-born Israel and his English partner Tara have sunk a cool &#163;150,000 of their own money into their trendy cafe bar D-Place, which offers a vast selection of fusion cuisine.

They believed they had found the WINNING FORMULA: great place, great music, great service, great food... and all at the right price.

Sounds promising... but from there on it's all DOWNHILL.

For the first two years, it all went swimmingly as Israel built up a mini-empire of five businesses... but the success didn't last long. Just three years later and they are all GONE - only D-Place remains and it's hanging by a thread.

It's a 24-carat NIGHTMARE.

The staff are at WAR, the plastic food is DIRE, the customers have evaporated, the restaurant is losing MONEY and the owners are at their WITS END. Something simply has to give or everyone is out of a job.

Faced with dysfunctional staff and a disastrous menu, Gordon is about to face the LONGEST WEEK of his professional life. Can he quell the panic, banish the deep fa</desc><sub-title>D-Place</sub-title></programme></tv>