<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530183000 -0400" stop="20260530190000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Linda and the girls attempt to build a loft bed for Louise in just one day; Bob and Gene host a group of gamers.</desc><sub-title>Loft in Bedslation</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530182901 -0400" stop="20260530185228 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>When George and Angie get into major financial trouble, Benny secretly asks Lydia, the second wife of George's estranged father, for help. Meanwhile, George does his best to obtain extra money-leading him to encounter some disreputable characters.</desc><sub-title>George Has Two Mommies</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530172551 -0400" stop="20260530191601 -0400"><title>Whiplash</title><desc>A promising young drummer enrolls at a cut-throat music conservatory where his dreams of greatness are mentored by an instructor who will stop at nothing to realize a student's potential.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530233000 +0100" stop="20260531000000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Uniform are looking for someone who is letting off distress flares inside letterboxes.  Melvin arrives on the scene of an attack.  Householder wants something done.   Hollis is back on the beat.  As he is responding to Melvin's call to assist, he knocks into a rider of a moped who takes off.  Fire Officer tells Cryer flares could be dangerous because of corrosion.  Hollis is swinging bag around containing flare gun.  Suspect has a thing about neighbourhood watch.   An elderly betting shop owner(ex villain) tells Burnside about another elderly villain who has come out of retirement to out a contract on him.  P.C. Turnham goes undercover.</desc><sub-title>Make My Day</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530182046 -0400" stop="20260530184435 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Racing Leathers, Evaporative Cooling Towers, Wood Rocking Chairs, and Wire Wheels and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Racing Leathers, Evaporative Cooling Towers, Wood Rocking Chairs, Wire Wheels</sub-title></programme></tv>