<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524183000 -0400" stop="20260524190000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Louise convinces her parents to cash in on the lucrative Valentine's Day dinner business, even though it means putting Bob and Linda's own Valentine's Day plans on hold. Meanwhile, Tina attends Tammy's Anti-Valentine's Day party.</desc><sub-title>Romancing the Beef</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524181218 -0400" stop="20260524183757 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>As Monica's biological clock ticks away like a time bomb, Carol goes into labor. Ross, Susan and Phoebe end up getting locked in a closet just as Carol's about to give birth to the baby. And Rachel flirts with an OB/GYN.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Birth</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524181318 -0400" stop="20260524202356 -0400"><title>Spider-Man 2</title><desc>Peter Parker is beset with troubles in his failing personal life as he battles a former brilliant scientist named Otto Octavius.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524233000 +0100" stop="20260525000000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Burnside goes to the funeral of an old villian, father of man suspected of the robbery.  A dog digs up the loot.   Melvin is talking to a boy playing hookey when he spota an armed robbery. He wrestles with the gunman but is knocked out.   An Irish plumber in for drunk and disorderly offers to unblock the toilets.  After unblocking them, he charges the station a call out fee.</desc><sub-title>Mickey Would Have Wanted It</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524174533 -0400" stop="20260524183827 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Jamie and Adam attempt to save themselves in a falling elevator by jumping just before it hits bottom. Then they challenge their imaginations and building skills as they try to create a homemade levitation machine.</desc><sub-title>Elevator of Death, Levitation Machine</sub-title></programme></tv>