<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518174500 -0400" stop="20260518183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>House treats a magician but comes to believe he's faking illness to cover up his own incompetence. Meanwhile, House pits the fellows against each other in his version of an immunity challenge.</desc><sub-title>You Don't Want to Know</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518173700 -0400" stop="20260518180049 -0400"><title>Superstore</title><desc>Amy's daughter Emma is without childcare and has to come to the store for the day. Unfortunately, this is against store policy, so when Glenn pulls Amy away to help him with a task, Jonah has to keep Amy's secret and an eye on Emma. Elsewhere Mateo and Cheyenne fight over a couch that is on sale because an elderly man passed away on it and Dina tries to catch a shoplifter.</desc><sub-title>Shoplifter</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260518172232 -0400" stop="20260518185629 -0400"><title>War of the Worlds</title><desc>Will Radford is a top analyst for Homeland Security who tracks potential threats through a mass surveillance program, until one day an attack by an unknown entity leads him to question whether the government is hiding something from him... and from the rest of the world.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260518223000 +0100" stop="20260518230000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>A fleeing Shir&#333; is eventually cornered by Rin, who offers to spare his life if he gives her his Command Seals. However, he refuses, prompting Rin to try and kill him. Both are then distracted by a scream downstairs and he and Rin find an unconscious girl. As Rin attempts to heal her, a dagger flies through an open door, aimed for Rin, but Shir&#333; blocks it with his arm, wounding himself in the process. He runs outside to find the female Servant, which is of the Rider class, and repels an attack by her. Shir&#333; considers summoning Saber via Command Seal, but decides it is too risky to get her involved and resolves to confront Rider himself. Rider resumes her assault, and Shir&#333; is nearly killed by her until Rin rescues him. At Rin's home, Shir&#333; and Rin decide to form a temporary truce to find Rider's Master.</desc><sub-title>Two Magi (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518175156 -0400" stop="20260518183907 -0400"><title>Richard Hammond's BIG</title><desc>Richard visits the world's tallest building: the Burj Khalifa in Dubai. His vertical mission includes climbing the biggest lightening conductor on earth!</desc><sub-title>Tallest Building on Earth</sub-title></programme></tv>