<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531174500 -0400" stop="20260531183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>Thirteen brings her one-night stand to the hospital after the woman has a seizure. However, the woman admits she slept with Thirteen just so she could get to House and have him diagnose her condition. Meanwhile, House continues to pay Lucas to spy on Wilson.</desc><sub-title>Lucky Thirteen</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531161725 -0400" stop="20260531182623 -0400"><title>Ted 2</title><desc>Newlywed couple Ted and Tami-Lynn want to have a baby, but in order to qualify to be a parent, Ted will have to prove he's a person in a court of law.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531175051 -0400" stop="20260531192826 -0400"><title>The Secret World of Arrietty</title><desc>The Clock family consists of three four-inch-tall people who live incognito among humans, borrowing only what they need to survive. Their quiet life changes when their teenage daughter, Arrietty, is discovered.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531223000 +0100" stop="20260531230000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>Shinji says things like how he has no intention of fighting and he was just dragged into this war. He asks to make an alliance with Shirou to go after Rin but Shirou refuses. Shinji says because he doesn't know magic other Masters can't detect him so that means Shinji isn't the other Master Rin was detecting, meaning there is a fourth one at the school. Before Shirou leaves Shinji tells Shirou about how one of the Masters has set up base at a temple.Shirou gets home and is yelled at by Saber and Rin, Rin having come over after Shirou didn't come home. Shirou tells them about Shinji and the Master at the temple.Shirou and Rin both agree, against Sabers judgment, that they should not attack the temple yet as they don't know what Servant and it may be a trap.Saber brings up again with Shirou the temple but Shirou insists that they won't be going.</desc><sub-title>Discordant Melody</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531175429 -0400" stop="20260531182100 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Your face is pretty remarkable. Whether you've got a baby face, a poker face, or a face only a mother could love... your identity is deeply rooted in your own unique face. And with over 40 muscles twisting and contorting, your face allows you to express a near infinite number of emotions and feelings. But not only are you capable of making faces -- your brain is also highly adept at recognizing what other peoples' faces are saying to you. In this episode about faces, we're going to mess with your mind and show you that there's more to a face than meets the eye.</desc><sub-title>Faces</sub-title></programme></tv>