<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518100000 -0400" stop="20260518110000 -0400"><title>Frasier</title><desc>Daphne's a wreck and finally confides her feelings for Niles to Frasier, who encourages her to talk with him. Meanwhile, Daphne's uncouth brother, Simon, continues to get on the family's nerves and Roz tries to scare up a proper date for Daphne's wedding after finding out an ex-boyfriend will be there. Niles makes a life-altering decision.</desc><sub-title>Something Borrowed, Someone Blue (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518095649 -0400" stop="20260518102056 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>At a banquet honouring her mother, Leslie tries to convince a local zoning official to support her park project. But sensing resistance, Lesie resorts to blackmail. Meanwhile, Tom and Mark ditch the festivities to hit the bars.</desc><sub-title>The Banquet</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260518095053 -0400" stop="20260518120648 -0400"><title>For a Few Dollars More</title><desc>Two bounty killers with similar intentions but different motivations team up to take down a psychotic Mexican outlaw before he and his gang can carry out an audacious bank robbery.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260518150000 +0100" stop="20260518160000 +0100"><title>The Chase (2009)</title><desc>Bradley Walsh and his criminally clever chaser are back for yet another battle of the brains. Can our contestants beat the Chaser, or will it be just another day at the office? Simon, Mel, Janice and Kier hope that together they can beat the Chaser and leave with thousands of pounds.</desc><sub-title>Episode 121</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518093920 -0400" stop="20260518103124 -0400"><title>Planet Earth</title><desc>Shallow seas cover only 8% of earth's surface, but contain the richest, most varied maritime life: from plankton and coral (literally vital for the very existence of reefs) to birds and from various invertebrates to mammals like seals, dolphins and whales and from sea snakes to countless fish species. Their ecological interaction is greatly varied and complex, often with nearby land to, even with deserts.</desc><sub-title>Shallow Seas</sub-title></programme></tv>