<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523073000 -0400" stop="20260523080000 -0400"><title>The Nanny</title><desc>Maxwell suspects Fran's therapist is pushing her into an affair.</desc><sub-title>The Nose Knows</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523072938 -0400" stop="20260523075351 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Due to his crippling debt, Jake faces losing his apartment, and asks Gina for help. Rosa and Charles clash with one of the weekend officers, and Holt and Terry ask their officers to conduct self-evaluations.</desc><sub-title>The Apartment</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523061753 -0400" stop="20260523093713 -0400"><title>Apocalypse Now</title><desc>At the height of the Vietnam war, Captain Benjamin Willard is sent on a dangerous mission that, officially, "does not exist, nor will it ever exist." His goal is to locate - and eliminate - a mysterious Green Beret Colonel named Walter Kurtz, who has been leading his personal army on illegal guerrilla missions into enemy territory.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523120000 +0100" stop="20260523130000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Saturday night at The Glass House Restaurant in Ambleside was a disaster. Orders in the kitchen were mixed up, the food wasn't cooked properly and the customers were complaining. Not only was the chef in tears, but the owners were on the brink of bankruptcy. A few months on, there have been some departures from the Glass House. Who is in charge of the kitchen now? And, more importantly, is Ramsay's Caesar salad still on the menu?</desc><sub-title>The Glass House (Revisited)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523073239 -0400" stop="20260523075757 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>This is a show about your brain and how it perceives motion. Evolving in a world that is constantly moving, the human brain had to develop a pretty sophisticated sense of motion in order to survive. This episode stops to ask some deceptively simple questions--What really is motion? Is the movement that you see real?</desc><sub-title>Motion Commotion</sub-title></programme></tv>