<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516161500 -0400" stop="20260516170000 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>Marci Maven is accused of negligent homicide because her neighbor claims that her dog killed his wife. But she claims her dog died a few days ago. So she turns to Monk, whom she's obsessed with, for help. When he refuses to see her, she buys him at a bachelor auction. When Monk tells her what happened, and when he looks at things, he discovers a few anomalies.</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk and His Biggest Fan</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516162646 -0400" stop="20260516165101 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie decides that she and her committee need to go door-to-door to gain support for the park project as well as support for an upcoming town hall meeting, but their mission does not go as planned. Meanwhile, Tom wanders away from the canvassing group and uses his own creative recruitment tactics.</desc><sub-title>Canvassing</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516154940 -0400" stop="20260516174358 -0400"><title>Promare</title><desc>A futuristic firefighting mecha service is created to protect the world.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260516213000 +0100" stop="20260516223000 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>Harry Saxon becomes Prime Minister and his reign of terror begins &#8211; but that's only the start of his ambitions, as he announces mankind's first contact with an alien race, the Toclafane. An audacious plan spanning the whole of time and space begins to close around the Earth, in the penultimate episode of Russell T Davies's Doctor Who.</desc><sub-title>The Sound of Drums (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516161626 -0400" stop="20260516164113 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>This is a show about your brain and the widely held myths you believe to be true. Through a series of fun and interactive games and experiments, you'll discover whether or not you only use 10% of your brain, if size really does matter and whether listening to Mozart actually makes you smarter.</desc><sub-title>Misconceptions</sub-title></programme></tv>