<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531144500 -0400" stop="20260531151500 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie takes the whole department camping in order to brainstorm new ideas. Meanwhile, Andy attempts a romantic gesture for April, while Ann gets nervous when Chris returns to Pawnee as the new city manager.</desc><sub-title>Camping</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531144825 -0400" stop="20260531152054 -0400"><title>Last Week Tonight with John Oliver</title><desc>The main story tonight concerns the upcoming in/out referendum regarding the UK's future status in the EU. John muses both sides of the issue, yet despite being torn, eventually endorses a position in what has become his own unique style. John also examines the NRA's political influence over gun legislation.</desc><sub-title>Brexit</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531134715 -0400" stop="20260531160642 -0400"><title>The Amazing Spider-Man</title><desc>After Peter Parker is bitten by a genetically altered spider, he gains newfound, spider-like powers and ventures out to save the city from the machinations of a mysterious reptilian foe.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531190000 +0100" stop="20260531200500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>The lads are in Lillehammer for their version of the Winter Olympics. So expect amongst other things: car ice-hockey - with Suzuki Swifts - Jeremy trying to drive the new Jaguar XK around the rink faster than a speed skater and Stig riding a snowmobile down the ski-jump. James and Jeremy compete against each other in a biathlon using an Audi Q7 and a Volvo XC90, with the loser having to eat yellow snow.

There's also a spectacular attempt to send a rocket-powered Mini down the ski-jump.</desc><sub-title>Winter Olympics Special</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531145018 -0400" stop="20260531154346 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>In the final programme, Gordon returns to Momma Cherri's Soul Food Shack, an intimate 40-seater in Brighton where he oversaw one of the most spectacular changes of fortune at a single venue. Owner Charita Jones was producing a menu of irresistible unique classics from the Deep South, but at the same facing financial disaster. The punters were missing, and so was her business acumen. But Gordon succeeded in shutting her out of the kitchen, getting the chef back on the boil and putting the soul back into the business.

Today Charita is fully-booked round the clock and bursting out of the Soul Shack to take on the 110-seater Momma Cherri's Big House. But expansion brings a different set of challenges, and she's still struggling to control her staff and manage her success. Has she got what it takes to make the next step up, or will she be forced to rethink her grand plans?</desc><sub-title>Momma Cherri's Soul Food Shack (Revisited)</sub-title></programme></tv>