<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522070000 -0400" stop="20260522073000 -0400"><title>The King of Queens</title><desc>In an attempt to go to Las Vegas for a weekend with the guys, Doug begins to build up credit by taking Carrie to a spa. Meanwhile, after hearing about Las Vegas, Arthur trains Spence on how to count cards, before visiting a small casino, being held for orphans.</desc><sub-title>Lost Vegas</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522070704 -0400" stop="20260522073104 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>The squad gets invited for Captain Holt's birthday party and they all try to impress his husband, Kevin. However, when Jake realises that him and Hitchcock are the only ones not able to bring in anything on an intellectual level, his drive to proof himself becomes more personal. Jake eventually uses what he does best, being a detective, to win Kevin over.</desc><sub-title>The Party</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522044939 -0400" stop="20260522074153 -0400"><title>Interstellar</title><desc>When Earth becomes uninhabitable in the future, a farmer and ex-NASA pilot, Joseph Cooper, is tasked to pilot a spacecraft, along with a team of researchers, to find a new planet for humans.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522120000 +0100" stop="20260522130000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>What's the BEST RECIPE for a successful restaurant? Top French chefs, the finest ingredients, food fit for a king...

Fine dining restaurant La Riviera in Inverness has it all and more.

All except one teeny weeny thing... CUSTOMERS. Without them, you don't stand a CHANCE.

And La Riviera is running out of TIME and MONEY.

La Riviera is on a MISSION: to bring sophisticated French cuisine to the home of haggis, tatties and deep-fried Mars bars. So it's the BEST of everything. It boasts a real DREAM COOKING TEAM: top French chef Loic Lefebvre who's worked in some of the best restaurants in the world and an impeccably-trained kitchen staff with Michelin star-studded backgrounds. The produce is ultra-fresh and top quality - the veg is flown in from France. Even the equipment is top of the league. So far, so good.

But delivering the very best costs... BIG TIME. Multi-millionaire owner Barry Larson is tearing his hair out as La Riviera is costing him a cool &#163;8,000 a week to run - and that's on t</desc><sub-title>La Riviera</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522072555 -0400" stop="20260522082801 -0400"><title>Rivers with Griff Rhys Jones</title><desc>Griff travels upstream from Kinlochleven into one of the most remote areas of Scotland.</desc><sub-title>Scotland</sub-title></programme></tv>