<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260528034500 -0400" stop="20260528043000 -0400"><title>The X-Files</title><desc>Five male teenagers in Connerville, Oklahoma were reported to have been struck by lightning, and one of them has survived. The most recent death draws Mulder and Scully in, and at the confrontation of local law enforcement, they must solve the case before they, too, are fried.</desc><sub-title>D.P.O.</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260528035331 -0400" stop="20260528042630 -0400"><title>Last Week Tonight with John Oliver</title><desc>John reflects on the aftermath of Paris attacks and how it affects refugees worldwide. Plus, he questions the usefulness of the U.S. penny, since minting the coins costs more than they're actually worth.</desc><sub-title>Refugees &amp; Pennies</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260528040506 -0400" stop="20260528062216 -0400"><title>Deadpool 2</title><desc>After losing Vanessa (Morena Baccarin), the love of his life, fourth-wall-breaking mercenary Wade Wilson, aka Deadpool (Ryan Reynolds), must assemble a team and protect a young mutant Russell Collins, aka Firefist (Julian Dennison), from Cable (Josh Brolin), a no-nonsense, dangerous cyborg from the future, and must also learn the most important lesson of all: to be part of a family again.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260528090000 +0100" stop="20260528093500 +0100"><title>Dad's Army</title><desc>Mainwaring promotes Frazer to Lance Corporal, thus causing friction between him and Jones. When Frazer starts getting above himself, Mainwaring rescinds the promotion.</desc><sub-title>A Stripe for Frazer</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260528035816 -0400" stop="20260528045046 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>La Gondola - a hotel and restaurant in Derby - strikes Gordon as being stuck in the past, and indeed its glory days were back in the 1970s. The challenge is to haul the staff, decor and cuisine into the 21st century and once again fill the dining room with happy customers.</desc><sub-title>La Gondola</sub-title></programme></tv>