<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518161500 -0400" stop="20260518170000 -0400"><title>Bones</title><desc>The flattened remains of a woman are found in a recycling plant, leading the team to a wedding planner, the woman's fiancee, and the owner of an online dating service. As the Squints work to solve the case, Bones and Booth are at odds when it appears that someone they know is cheating on a friend/colleague.</desc><sub-title>The Cinderella in the Cardboard</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518162428 -0400" stop="20260518164738 -0400"><title>Everybody Hates Chris</title><desc>When Julius buys a big crate of sausage, he makes everyone eat it with every meal. But Tonya refuses to, causing friction between the pair. While at school, Chris is sentenced to 3 days of detention after a rumour goes round about him beating up the schoo</desc><sub-title>Everybody Hates Sausage</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260518154657 -0400" stop="20260518172232 -0400"><title>The Super Mario Bros. Movie</title><desc>A Brooklyn plumber named Mario travels through the Mushroom Kingdom with a princess named Peach and an anthropomorphic mushroom named Toad to find Mario's brother, Luigi, and to save the world from a ruthless fire-breathing Koopa named Bowser.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260518210500 +0100" stop="20260518220000 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>Trainee doctor Martha Jones has her hands full balancing her medical studies with placating her demanding family. So the last thing she needs is to find that the hospital where she works has been transported to the moon, where it's invaded by an overbearing alien police force. There she encounters a patient called John Smith, who seems curiously at ease with the situation&#8230;</desc><sub-title>Smith and Jones</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518163343 -0400" stop="20260518172707 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 13</sub-title></programme></tv>