<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530123000 -0400" stop="20260530131500 -0400"><title>Kitchen Nightmares (US)</title><desc>Gordon travels to the town of Easton, PA, where he tries to wake up a mother and son pairing who are running their Italian restaurant into the ground.</desc><sub-title>Bella Luna</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530123801 -0400" stop="20260530130152 -0400"><title>Adam Ruins Everything</title><desc>Straight from the red carpet (and with the help of celebrity guests Rachel Bloom and Ariana Madix), Adam exposes the hidden truths behind Hollywood's glitz and glamour, from the clothes stars wear to the process behind movie ratings.</desc><sub-title>Adam Ruins Hollywood</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530101908 -0400" stop="20260530130234 -0400"><title>Hamilton</title><desc>The real life of one of America's foremost founding fathers and first Secretary of the Treasury, Alexander Hamilton. Captured live on Broadway from the Richard Rodgers Theater with the original Broadway cast.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530173000 +0100" stop="20260530180000 +0100"><title>Would I Lie to You?</title><desc>Rob Brydon hosts the comedy panel show, with team captains David Mitchell and Lee Mack and guest panellists Kelvin MacKenzie, Christine Bleakley, Frankie Boyle and Jack Whitehall.</desc><sub-title>Jack Whitehall, Kelvin McKenzie, Christine Bleakley, Frankie Boyle</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530123716 -0400" stop="20260530130448 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The second visit is to The Arches on the Isle of Man where ex-demolition man Phil Routledge is proud of his super-modern B&amp;B, which was voted the best in the Isle of Man.

On arrival, his guests are blown away by the views, and fellow Isle of Man residents John and Fiona Anderson lap up the his and hers bath. But the lack of instructions for the state-of-the art gadgetry leaves guest Julie Brogan stumped.

Phil wins over his guests after an afternoon of scuba diving in the Arches' own pool, and in the morning, Phil's wife Jill takes charge in the kitchen where some 'perfect' eggs Benedict puts the pressure on the mainlanders who are hosting next.</desc><sub-title>The Arches</sub-title></programme></tv>