<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260519174500 -0400" stop="20260519183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>Under Cuddy&#8217;s pressure to choose his team, House gives the candidates a case of a former punk rock star who is a drug user. Whoever diagnoses the patient is going to have a future as a member of House&#8217;s team.</desc><sub-title>Games</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260519180519 -0400" stop="20260519183009 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Amy hosts Thanksgiving dinner for the precinct in an effort to get Holt to be her mentor, but Holt and Jake leave early and the rest hate her cooking.</desc><sub-title>Thanksgiving</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260519164116 -0400" stop="20260519184214 -0400"><title>Tetris</title><desc>An enterprising game developer risks everything in a race to outmaneuver duplicitous insiders to negotiate a deal with Soviet Union bureaucrats for the international licensing rights to what would eventually become one of the most recognizable and widely played games in history.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260519230000 +0100" stop="20260519233000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>A fleeing Shir&#333; is eventually cornered by Rin, who offers to spare his life if he gives her his Command Seals. However, he refuses, prompting Rin to try and kill him. Both are then distracted by a scream downstairs and he and Rin find an unconscious girl. As Rin attempts to heal her, a dagger flies through an open door, aimed for Rin, but Shir&#333; blocks it with his arm, wounding himself in the process. He runs outside to find the female Servant, which is of the Rider class, and repels an attack by her. Shir&#333; considers summoning Saber via Command Seal, but decides it is too risky to get her involved and resolves to confront Rider himself. Rider resumes her assault, and Shir&#333; is nearly killed by her until Rin rescues him. At Rin's home, Shir&#333; and Rin decide to form a temporary truce to find Rider's Master.</desc><sub-title>Two Magi (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260519180444 -0400" stop="20260519185809 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 20</sub-title></programme></tv>