<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517151500 -0400" stop="20260517154500 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie accidentally finds out that Tom is getting a divorce and tries to lift his spirits by sending him to dinner and a strip club, but Tom doesn't tell her that it was just a sham Green Card marriage.</desc><sub-title>Tom's Divorce</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517151152 -0400" stop="20260517164910 -0400"><title>Wayne's World 2</title><desc>Wayne is back, this time trying to organize a rock festival with help from friend Garth and the spirit of Jim Morrison (Doors). Meanwhile, his girlfriend's manager is busy trying to woo her away from Wayne and move her to LA. Life gets interesting when Wayne must rush from the concert to try and stop the wedding. Aerosmith are featured at the concert.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517153428 -0400" stop="20260517175744 -0400"><title>Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith</title><desc>As the Clone Wars nears its end, Obi-Wan Kenobi pursues a new threat, while Anakin Skywalker is lured by Chancellor Palpatine into a sinister plot for galactic domination.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517201500 +0100" stop="20260517210000 +0100"><title>An Idiot Abroad</title><desc>Karl travels to Africa to see wild gorillas. Prior to visiting the gorillas, Ricky and Steve send Karl to teach at a school, rebuild a hut, go bungee jumping, visit a domesticated hippo, cook for a king, and go animal tracking.</desc><sub-title>Meet a Gorilla</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517145639 -0400" stop="20260517155755 -0400"><title>Planet Earth II</title><desc>From vast herds to epic predator and prey battles, Grasslands are home to huge spectacles.</desc><sub-title>Grasslands</sub-title></programme></tv>