<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524161500 -0400" stop="20260524170000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>A former music producer who had recently---and suddenly---converted to Hasidic Judaism collapses at her wedding, and House suspects that the reasons behind her sudden conversion might also have something to do with her mysterious illness. Meanwhile, Wilson is dating a woman whose personality is a lot like House's.</desc><sub-title>Don't Ever Change</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524163320 -0400" stop="20260524165839 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Chandler discovers that he and Rachel had an intimate moment in her dream. After revealing to her young boyfriend that she is older than she said, he reveals he is a high school senior. When Phoebe temps as Chandler's secretary, he discovers that his colleagues don't like him.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Ick Factor</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524141028 -0400" stop="20260524164806 -0400"><title>Pulp Fiction</title><desc>A burger-loving hit man, his philosophical partner, a drug-addled gangster's moll and a washed-up boxer converge in this sprawling, comedic crime caper. Their adventures unfurl in three stories that ingeniously trip back and forth in time.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524210500 +0100" stop="20260524220000 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>In a far-flung galaxy, saboteurs are at work, and crew members are being possessed. The TARDIS crew find themselves in the 42nd century on a spaceship, SS Pentallian, slowly being pulled into a sun, and must find a way to survive</desc><sub-title>42</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524162131 -0400" stop="20260524164918 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The group are off to Great Yarmouth to stay in Sue's dog friendly Seashells Guesthouse. After revealing that she allows dogs to sleep in the beds during the last B&amp;B visit, no one knows quite what to expect.

All the guests are blown away by the doggy-themed exterior. The interior is equally memorable for Nancy, who finds dog hairs under the duvet.

Spirits are high during the afternoon as Sue gives her guests a taste of Great Yarmouth beachside fun, such as a horse and trap ride and a game of bingo.

Over dinner, the jovial mood is crushed when Nancy brings up the issues of dogs sleeping in the beds and Sue allowing smoking in the bedrooms.

Tempers are raised and accusations fly. At feedback time, Sue goes into a combative mood when she reads Nancy's frank comments.</desc><sub-title>Seashells Guesthouse, Great Yarmouth</sub-title></programme></tv>