<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260526161500 -0400" stop="20260526170000 -0400"><title>Bones</title><desc>Brennan and Booth are asked to investigate the death of a man who was murdered for the secret contents of his briefcase. They suspect that secret operatives are at work, and their theory is proven correct when they find the liquefied remains of a CIA agent in the trunk of a car. Meanwhile, Brennan's new best-selling book causes tension between her and Booth, and Wendell loses his scholarship.</desc><sub-title>The Bond in the Boot</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260526162223 -0400" stop="20260526164827 -0400"><title>Superstore</title><desc>Dina throws a wrench in everyone's Halloween plans when something goes missing from the store and declares that no employee can leave until someone confesses to stealing.</desc><sub-title>Halloween Theft</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260526142608 -0400" stop="20260526162945 -0400"><title>The Social Network</title><desc>As Harvard student Mark Zuckerberg creates the social networking site that would become known as Facebook, he is sued by the twins who claimed he stole their idea and by the co-founder who was later squeezed out of the business.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260526154633 -0400" stop="20260526163941 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>The mythbusters are testing a myth of operatic proportions-- Can a singer really break glass with just their voice? Ex rock singer, Jaime Vendera attempts a world first! Tory takes on building an explosive jet engine out of vacuum cleaner parts.</desc><sub-title>Breaking Glass</sub-title></programme></tv>