<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524083000 -0400" stop="20260524090000 -0400"><title>3rd Rock from the Sun</title><desc>Dick tries to get Mary back and wants to surprise her with champagne when she's in the school library. The real surprise is that Dick and Mary find themselves locked in the library overnight. Tommy, Sally and Harry don't want Dick and Mary to get back together and try to find them. They go to Mary's house, don't find them but decide to stay for the night. Sally even hosts a Tupperware party Mary was supposed to host.</desc><sub-title>Stuck with Dick</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524082648 -0400" stop="20260524085030 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>When Michael slips some sly references about Pam in his conversations with Jim, Jim quickly tries to do damage control to make sure that no one else in the office finds about his crush on Pam, all while slamming himself with regret for ever telling Michael in the first place. Jim goes to drastic measures, even bonding with Michael at a Hooters restaurant for lunch. Nonetheless, Jim's efforts do little to keep Michael from revealing the secret, but Jim smooths the situation over with Pam to make it seem like nothing more than a tiny crush in the past. Meanwhile, Dwight conducts an investigation about Oscar's mysterious absence from work, and what Dwight finds, though it goes way over his head, is surprising.</desc><sub-title>The Secret</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524073312 -0400" stop="20260524090312 -0400"><title>Coneheads</title><desc>A pair of aliens arrive on Earth to prepare for invasion, but crash instead. With enormous cone-shaped heads, robotlike walks and an appetite for toilet paper, aliens Beldar and Prymatt don't exactly blend in with the population of Paramus, N.J. But for some reason, everyone believes them when they say they're from France.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524133000 +0100" stop="20260524140000 +0100"><title>Fate/Apocrypha</title><desc>Berserker of Red approaches the Black Faction stronghold. The Yggdmillennia clan and their Servants seize the opportunity to take action.</desc><sub-title>Life's Cost, Death's Redemption</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524080416 -0400" stop="20260524083129 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Jan and William Cheeseman have achieved a Five-Star Gold rating at 38 St Giles in Norwich, but the pursuit of perfection has been known to take its toll on this volatile pair.

Things are anything but perfect for Galia when she arrives. Unhappy with her room due to the road noise, she asks to be moved. Luckily a day on the race track gives Galia something to smile about as she has the ride of her life.

At breakfast time, Jan and William go into meltdown in the kitchen. But at the breakfast table the guests are none the wiser.</desc><sub-title>38 St Giles, Norwich</sub-title></programme></tv>