<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530034500 -0400" stop="20260530043000 -0400"><title>The X-Files</title><desc>Mulder is trapped inside a train car which contains a suspected alien-human hybrid and also a bomb, while Scully pursues the truth about her abduction and the mystery behind the implant in her neck.</desc><sub-title>731 (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530035812 -0400" stop="20260530042238 -0400"><title>New Girl</title><desc>When the gang attempts to juggle multiple holiday parties in one night, Jess tries to avoid a remorseful Sam, Nick tries to keep up with a sexually adventurous Angie and Winston panics when he gets a cranberry stuck in his ear.</desc><sub-title>Santa</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530014309 -0400" stop="20260530041141 -0400"><title>Goodfellas</title><desc>Henry Hill recounts his life in the mob, from his teenage years to his eventual downfall. Immersed in organized crime, he experiences wealth, power, and violence alongside friends Jimmy Conway and Tommy DeVito. The film blends crime, drama, and dark humor, exploring loyalty, ambition, betrayal, and the consequences of criminal life. Themes of family, morality, and the fleeting nature of power underpin the story.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530090000 +0100" stop="20260530093500 +0100"><title>Dad's Army</title><desc>Capt. Mainwaring teaches the platoon the tactical use of the phone system when a German plane crashes into the town's reservoir. Because Mainwaring and Wilson cannot decide what to do it is left to Walker to come up with a plan to make the Germans surrender.</desc><sub-title>The Lion Has Phones</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530035528 -0400" stop="20260530042301 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>A new competition kicks off at Abbey House in Penrith, Cumbria, where Ian Sugden and his wife Sam treat their guests to an afternoon on the firing range and fancy bacon for breakfast.</desc><sub-title>Abbey House</sub-title></programme></tv>