<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523043000 -0400" stop="20260523051500 -0400"><title>Buffy the Vampire Slayer</title><desc>While Riley's health begins to deteriorate, Spike and Harmony force a surgeon to remove the behavior modification chip embedded in Spike's brain.</desc><sub-title>Out of My Mind</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523042952 -0400" stop="20260523045531 -0400"><title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title><desc>Dennis joins up with an environmentalist group, but his altruistic intentions quickly sour when he's snubbed by the activists. Dee and Mac decide to raise a baby they find in the dumpster, but quickly find out that it's not nearly as fun as they thought it would be, and Frank and Charlie take the concept of recycling a bit too far.</desc><sub-title>The Gang Finds a Dumpster Baby</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523043349 -0400" stop="20260523061753 -0400"><title>Finding Nemo</title><desc>Nemo, an adventurous young clownfish, is unexpectedly taken from his Great Barrier Reef home to a dentist's office aquarium. It's up to his worrisome father Marlin and a friendly but forgetful fish Dory to bring Nemo home -- meeting vegetarian sharks, surfer dude turtles, hypnotic jellyfish, hungry seagulls, and more along the way.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523093500 +0100" stop="20260523100000 +0100"><title>Impractical Jokers</title><desc>The four Jokers compete to pin the most balloons onto unsuspecting grocery shoppers, complete awkward tasks while posing as salesmen at a musical instrument store, and try to get complimented on their not-so-fashionable outfits. The loser ruffles people's feathers in the park - "sorry, not sorry!"</desc><sub-title>Sorry for Your Loss</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523045319 -0400" stop="20260523054728 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Could a person survive a leap from a bridge by throwing a hammer in the water first? Is it possible to survive being buried alive? Can cola really remove bloodstains, clean rust or cook a steak?</desc><sub-title>Buried Alive</sub-title></programme></tv>