<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523110000 -0400" stop="20260523114500 -0400"><title>Hell's Kitchen (US)</title><desc>The teams prepare dinner for boxing legend Mike Tyson and racecar driver Kurt Busch.</desc><sub-title>Temping the Meat</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523110121 -0400" stop="20260523112653 -0400"><title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title><desc>When the Philadelphia Eagles have open tryouts, Dennis, Mac, and Dee all try out. And while watching the tryouts, Frank and Charlie find out that the Mcpoyles are there too. Being that Frank needs to use the restroom, he must use the Mcboyles bathroom but first needs to take some of their milk to get in, which seems not to be only milk.</desc><sub-title>The Gang Gets Invincible</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523111233 -0400" stop="20260523132018 -0400"><title>Red One</title><desc>After Santa Claus -- Code Name: RED ONE -- is kidnapped, the North Pole's Head of Security (Dwayne Johnson) must team up with the world's most infamous bounty hunter and notorious hacker (Chris Evans) in a globe-trotting, action-packed mission to save Christmas.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523160000 +0100" stop="20260523164500 +0100"><title>Pointless</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 7</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523110032 -0400" stop="20260523112819 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Deborah Morrison and Wayne Bingham open their doors in Torquay, where a game of archery causes allegations of unfair play to fly.

While Melvyn and Sindy are curious to know if the chandelier's sturdy enough to do some swinging, Gill and Pete are concerned over the mismatching type-faces on the in-room brochure, which is apparently a cardinal B&amp;B sin. At dinner time the competitors' true feelings surface - with accusations of incoherent branding and imperfect websites.</desc><sub-title>Braddon Hall, Torquay</sub-title></programme></tv>