<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523200000 -0400" stop="20260523210000 -0400"><title>Salvage Hunters</title><desc>Drew and Tee fly to Norway where they set out on a thousand-mile adventure. Although concerned the prices may be out of reach, Drew seals his first Norwegian deal at an old sawmill turned gallery. Elsewhere, the chaps comb through a sprawling collection of classic car parts. At a wildlife park near Tunhovd, Drew is keen to buy antlers and skulls. Drew and Tee get a warm welcome from the owner of a remote manor farm.</desc><sub-title>Episode 5</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523195159 -0400" stop="20260523201614 -0400"><title>The Goldbergs (2013)</title><desc>Murray (Jeff Garlin) intervenes when Adam (Sean Giambrone) seeks Beverly's (Wendi McLendon-Covey) help to avoid a national physical fitness test. Barry (Troy Gentile) woos Erica's (Hayley Orrantia) French pen pal (guest star Bella Dayne).</desc><sub-title>The President's Fitness Test</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523184506 -0400" stop="20260523203833 -0400"><title>Sonic the Hedgehog 3</title><desc>Sonic, Knuckles, and Tails reunite against a powerful new adversary, Shadow, a mysterious villain with powers unlike anything they have faced before. With their abilities outmatched, Team Sonic must seek out an unlikely alliance.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524010000 +0100" stop="20260524013000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>Saber yelled at Shirou for not summoning her when he was in danger. Saber starts to go to school with Shirou. When Rin appears and says she will walk with Shirou to school, Saber allowing this after Rin talked to her. She explained that this way enemies may think it's a trap to not see Saber with him so they are less likely to attack.Rin explains that there should be spell marks around the school and if they destroy those it will delay the activation of the force field but not destroy it, and most likely force the master out of hiding. After school Shirou and Rin work to find spell marks and destroy them. They end up destroying a good amount of them and call it a night.On the way home, before Shirou gets anywhere but after Rin leaves he feels something really strong. He goes to investigate it and feels its coming from the archery club.</desc><sub-title>Despicable Act</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523195152 -0400" stop="20260523201754 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Bet you could explain something as basic as how a zipper works? Or correctly draw something as simple as a bicycle? If you said yes, you likely bet wrong... but don't worry it's not just you! When you stop and think about it, you're probably not that aware of all of the things you don't understand. The fact is we go through our daily lives feeling pretty confident in our knowledge and understanding of the world, but that confidence is mostly an illusion. In this episode of Brain Games, we'll show you firsthand just how the "illusion of knowledge" plagues the human brain and why we fall victim, again and again, to the notion that we understand more than we actually do.</desc><sub-title>What You Don't Know</sub-title></programme></tv>