<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524131500 -0400" stop="20260524134500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>An unexpected third wheel puts a damper on Jake and Amy's tropical honeymoon. Back at the Nine-Nine, Terry experiences a crisis of confidence.</desc><sub-title>Honeymoon</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524133040 -0400" stop="20260524135450 -0400"><title>Archer (2009)</title><desc>When a mysterious stranger summons Malory and her intrepid ISIS agents to Monaco, all bets are off! Well, actually all bets are on. Because Monaco is basically one giant casino, and Archer has $4 million in untraceable bearer bonds. Also, it's Gran Prix week, so you can just forget getting a hotel room</desc><sub-title>Jeu Monegasque</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524123253 -0400" stop="20260524141028 -0400"><title>The Secret World of Arrietty</title><desc>The Clock family consists of three four-inch-tall people who live incognito among humans, borrowing only what they need to survive. Their quiet life changes when their teenage daughter, Arrietty, is discovered.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524180000 +0100" stop="20260524184500 +0100"><title>House</title><desc>Chaos ensues after Chase's negligence leads to the death of a female patient. Now, after an inquiry from the hospital board, and a subpoena from the patient's brother, it's up to Stacey to protect Chase's career, as well as House's.</desc><sub-title>The Mistake</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524132445 -0400" stop="20260524135234 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>First to host are husband-and-wife team Paul Billington and Flora Loizou from Silverwood Lodge in Cambridgeshire, the only couple in this contest.

As the hosts show their three female guests to their rooms, Caroline, owner of The Dean B&amp;B, has a frosty view of the fact that they don't live on site.

The hosts try to impress their guests by taking them punting down the Cam, but Sue from Seashells Guesthouse almost manages to capsize the group.

Over dinner, straight-talking Nancy from The Old Court Guesthouse suggests that not living on site compromises the hosts' attention to customer needs.

Come morning, Caroline has been kept awake all night by the noisy road and Nancy's TV 'doesn't work'. When the hosts read the frank feedback they are left livid and accusations of foul play fly.</desc><sub-title>Silverwood Lodge, Cambridgeshire</sub-title></programme></tv>